Anjali Dhatwalia

+91-981-00-89949

anjali.dhatwalia@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Trustworthy and dedicated teacher, educator and facilitator of pre-primary and primary world school students; more than 12 years of experience in International Board leading world schools in India with exemplary track record of growing and developing young minds

EDUCATION

Modern Montessori International, London Diploma in Early Childhood Courses	2005-2006
Maharashtra University Bachelor of Arts	1994-1997
College of Architecture, Nashik Diploma in Interior Designing and Decoration	1996
Barnes School, Deolali ICSE	1992

WORK EXPERIENCE

MIT Vishwashanti Gurukul World School

July 2014- current

Home Room Teacher Primary Years Program

The Heritage School July 2007- March 2014

Home Room Teacher & Math Coordinator

Ryan International School July 2006- May 2007

Class Teacher

ADDITIONAL

• Creative content writer 2 years

Hazelnut Group, Justwords Consulting, Differential Imaging, Crescendo and miscellaneous content writing firms

• Website content for Mtalkies and blogs for evduniya.com Project Based

• Website Building - Wordpress 3 Years

Chalo Africa as Information Specialist

• Social Media Management 1 Year